Juliano Daniel Marcelino, M.Sc. System and Business Analyst

Life Philosophy

I enjoy help people (and companies) to solve problems.

Profile

Solid experience in IT and customer support, IT management, governance, consultant and teaching experience, on worldwide companies and organizations.

Hard skills includes business and systems analysis, software development, among other technologies, as well in agile methodologies and lean IT.

My main soft skills are ethics, teamwork, organization, QC-Story, communication, negotiation and flexibility.

Experience

Remote and On-site postgraduate and graduate classes and mentoring thesis in technology and engineering.

@ 09/19 - 02/21 ■ SENAI/SC - Jaraguá do Sul

Remote and On-site undergraduate professor.

🔊 07/15 - 04/19 🛘 📕 Catholic University Center Santa Catarina

Remote and On-site undergraduate professor.

Ø 09/12 - 12/13 ■ Anhanguera Educational

On-site postgraduate and extension projects mentoring.

🔊 09/11 - 02/13 🛮 📕 Delinea Education Technology

Remote technical writer and professor.

🔊 02/09 - 02/12 🏻 🌉 SENAI/SC – Jaraguá do Sul

IT and Business Management Specialist, coordinator of the computer architecture and operating systems laboratory.

2008 - 2009 FCJ – Cenecista College of Joinville Professor in Administration and Software Development.

②2008 - 2009 ■ CEDB – Dom Bosco Educational Center
Mentoring courses in IT and Administration.

2007 - 2008 MINPG – National Postgraduate Institute
Assistant professor and tech/educational consultant.

2007 - 2008 SoftExpert Automation
Project manager and consultant in EDI, BPM, BSC, SWOT,

KPI, KB, QA and SPLAN management systems.

🗓 2003 - 2006 🛮 📕 Datasul/NeoGrid

Deployment and integration in ERP, EDI, CRM, B2B, B2C, e/c-Commerce, VMI, JIT, forecast, kanban, and SCI.



Keep in touch

@ juliano@jmarcelino.com.br

4 +55 (47) 99199-4901

Jaraguá do Sul - SC - Brazil

ojmarcelino

in ojmarcelino

Certifications

② 2020 ► Kanban Institute
Kanban Foundation (KIKF)

🔊 2020 🔁 CertiProf

Scrum Foundations Professional

Certificate (SPFC)

Education

@ 2019 ► UniSociesc

Masters of Science in Production

Engineering, emphasis on Lean IT.

2012 🔁 Uniasselvi

MBA in Teaching to Higher Education.

2008 ≥INPG (pending diploma)
MBA in Project Management.

2007 ≥Univille

Bachelor in Information Systems.

Languages

(CEFR)

en–US C2 C2 C1 C1 C2
es–MX B2 B2 B1 A2 B1
pt–BR Native language
Libras–BR